Welcome to the Tapestry Engine demo, thanks for checking it out.

Tapestry engine is a 2D side-scroller engine written from scratch in C++ using the SDL2 library. 
Pretty much everything it does I coded myself.

This demo serves to demonstrate all the features and systems I've implemented so far.
You may encounter crashes or other bugs in this demo, it's a work in progress.

Controls:

←↑→↓ - Move left, right, jump, and drop down
q    - Draw and sheath your weapon
w    - Swing your weapon if it's drawn
e    - Interact, push to talk to characters, use doors etc.

If you have any questions I can be contacted at:

charles.s.baptista@gmail.com
or
baptistac1@wit.edu

To see some of my other work visit my website charlesbaptista.com

The art for this demo was created by Sofia Baptista - sofiabaptistacrafts.wordpress.com